<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:lang="en" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xml:id="pulpmags_asl19050311">
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title n="Minimum TEI Header for Issue-Level Markup (P5)"/>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <publisher n="The Pulp Magazines Project Mark II Grant v5"/>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p n="Electronic Transcription from Full-Text OCR Output"/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <front>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="00a" facs="00a"/>
                <space/>
                <div type="cover">
                    <ab rend="block">
                        <term type="editionIssue">No. 5</term>
                        <term type="editionPrice">5 Cents</term>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <title type="main" level="j" rend="logo">All-Sports Library</title>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <title type="main" level="m">JACK LIGHTFOOT IN THE WOODS</title>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <title type="sub" level="s">OR, Taking The Hermit Trout Of Simm's Hole</title>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="byline">By <persName role="illustrator">Maurice Stevens</persName></span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <hi rend="small-text block">There was a sudden splash, a flash of silver in the air, and a shout from Lafe, for Jack Lightfoot
                            had actually hooked the foxy old trout of the swimming-hole.</hi>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
        </front>
        <body>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="00b" facs="00b"/>
                <ab>[Blank Page]</ab>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="00c" facs="00c"/>
                <div type="editorialMatter">
                    <ab>
                        <hi rend="small-text">Publisher's Note: "Teach the American boy how to become an athlete, and lay the foundation for a
                            Constitution greater than that of the United States."--Wise sayings from "Tip Top." There has never been a time when the
                            boys of this great country took so keen an Interest in all manly and health-giving sports as they do to-day. As proof of
                            this witness the record-breaking throngs that attend college struggles on the gridiron, as well as athletic and baseball
                            games, and other tests of endurance and skill. In a multitude of other channels this love for the "life strenuous" is
                            making itself manifest, so that, as a nation, we are rapidly forging to the front as seekers of honest sport. Recognizing
                            this "handwriting on the wall," we have concluded that the time has arrived to give this vast army of young enthusiasts a
                            publication devoted exclusively to invigorating out-door life. We feel we are justified in anticipating a warm response
                            from our sturdy American boys, who are sure to revel in the stirring phases of sport and adventure, through which our
                            characters pass from week to week.</hi>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="masthead" part="I">
                    <ab>
                        <title type="main" level="j" rend="logo">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY</title>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="statement">
                    <ab>
                        <hi rend="small-text">Issued <term type="frequency">Weekly</term>. By Subscription <term type="subscPrice">$2.50 per
                                year</term>. Entered according to Act of Congress in the year <date>1905</date>, in the Office of the
                                <roleName>Librarian of Congress</roleName>, <placeName>Washington, D. C.</placeName>, by <orgName role="publisher">The
                                Winner Library Co.</orgName>, 2 Duane St. <placeName>New York, N. Y.</placeName>
                        </hi>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="masthead" part="F">
                    <ab>
                        <term type="editionIssue">No. 5</term>. <placeName>NEW YORK</placeName>, <date>March 11, 1905</date>. Price <term
                            type="editionPrice">Five Cents</term>. </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="contents">
                    <ab>
                        <title type="main" level="m">JACK LIGHTFOOT IN THE WOODS;</title>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <title type="sub" level="s">OR, Taking the Hermit Trout of Simm's Hole.</title>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="byline">By <persName role="author">MAURICE STEVENS</persName>.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHARACTERS IN THIS STORY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot, the best all-round athlete in Cranford or vicinity,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a lad clean of eye, clean of speech, and, after he had conquered a few</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of his faults, possessed of a faculty for doing things while others were</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">talking:, that by degrees caused him to be looked upon as the natural</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">leader in all the sports Young America delights in--a boy who in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">learning to conquer himself put the power into his hands to wrest</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">victory from others.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot, Jack's cousin, and sometimes his rival; though</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">their striving for the mastery was always of the friendly, generous</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">kind. Tom was called the "Book-Worm" by his fellows, on ac-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">count of his love for studying such secrets of nature as practical</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">observers have discovered and published; so that he possessed a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fund of general knowledge calculated to prove useful when his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wandering spirit took him abroad into strange lands.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen, of impulsive, nervous temperament, one of those who</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">followed the newcomer, Birkett, being dazzled by the dash of his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">manner, and the free way in which he flung money around.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nat Kimball, an undersized fellow, whose liobby was the study of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jiu-jitsu, and who had a dread of germs.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe Lampton, a big, hulking chap, with an ever present craving</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for something to eat. Lafe always had his appetite along, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">proved a stanch friend of our hero through thick and thin.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bob Brewster, a brawny lad, against whom Kimball tried his Jap</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tricks with poor results.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul Messenger, one of Jack's cronies, and called "Fighting Saul"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">by his mates.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nicholas Flint, who had a rod in pickle for Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold, Flint's ally in mischief making.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kennedy, the town constable.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg Brown, an odd character living near the "ole swimmin' hole."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jerry Mulligan, the jolly owner of a cart and horse.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ezra Bean, who delights to play the wild man, and scare honest</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">people by appearing as a ghost.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER I.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE HAUNTED GYM.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Whack, crack! whack, crack! Lub-brub-blub!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bang! Thump!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">These were the sounds that came from the gymna-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sium over the old carriage shop and caused Jack Light-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foot and the boys with him to jump for the doorway,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for the purpose of investigating.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels!" Ned Skeen gasped, as the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sounds continued. "Hear that? It's getting worse."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Even lazy Lafe Lampton was stirred into a quick</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">run.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The boys had been near the gym, on their. Way to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it for a meeting of the high-school athletic club was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to be held there that night.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="002" facs="002"/>
                <fw place="top">2 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They had expected to light the lamps and get the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fire to going well in the big stove, so that everything</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">would be comfortable when the other members ar-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rived.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Thump! Crack! Blub-rub-bub! Whang, thump!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jiminy crickets!" said Lafe. "Somebody's got in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">there and is smashing everything up for us."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">That was the thought of all.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They knew they had some enemies in Cranford;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and they suspected these evil wishers, rather than any</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of their rivals of the Cranford Academy club.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Yet there were some members of the academy or-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ganization who were mean enough, they belieyed, to do-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that very thing--smash up the apparatus in the high-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">school gym.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It may be well to explain to any who have not read</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the previous stories in this series that the gymnasium,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">spoken of here as the high-school gym, did not belong</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to the high school in any proper sense, but to the club</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of young students, whose captain and leader was Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lightfoot.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The clubroom and gym occupied the upper floor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Of an old ind abandoned carriage shop, and was given,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">refit free, to the boys by Norwell Strawn, proprietor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of Strawn's, dry-goods store, whose daughter, Kate,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had been saved from drowning by Jack Lightfoot at a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">time when she skated into a hole in the ice of Cran-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ford Lake.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Wow! the scamp must be tearing the doors down!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said Bob Brewster, the big, red-haired giant of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">elub. "If I get my grippers on him I'll twist his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">neck."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We'll paste him for that, fellows!" cried Ned</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Skeen.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot had done more running than talking,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and reached the door first.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He fitted the key quickly to the lock and flung the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">door open.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then the boys raced for the stairs that led to the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">upper floor.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Before they gained the stairway the sounds hi</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ceased.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Go outside, some of you," Jack commanded. "He</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">may try to get out by the windows and jump down</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">from the shed roof."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bill Brewster and Nat Kimball turned back, Nat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fairly falling on himself as he struggled to get out of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the door quickly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack mounted lightly to the top floor, with Nat,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Skeen and Lafe Lampton at his heels.</span>
                    </ab>

                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The gym was still dark--so dark that when they</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">reached the door at the head of the stairs and had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thrown it open they could not even see the furnishing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They stood there a moment, breathing hard and lis-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tening.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">There was not a sound, other than what they made</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">themselves.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Look lively out there; don't let him get off the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">roof!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack shouted this to the boys outside.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then, with trembling fingers, he struck a match.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">One of the kerosene lamps used in lighting the gym</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was on a stand by the door, and when the flame of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">match revealed nothing he lit the lamp.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He isn't in here!" said Skeen, and turned to de-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">scend the stairs, in order to watch from the outside.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In doing so he stumbled and fell half the length of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the stairway, bringing up at the bottom with a clatter.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Any bones broke?" Jack queried.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"N-no; I'm all right!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With a sense of relief they heard him leap up.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">One of the boys outside, having heard that clatter</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">came bounding through the doorway.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Stay outside!" Skeen bellowed at him. "I don't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">think he's in the gym."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Then he's on the roof," Brewster was heard to de-</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="003" facs="003"/>
                <fw place="top">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY 3</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">clare. "He hasn't got off of it, for we've been watch-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack now advanced into the gymnasium, holding the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lamp before him, and was followed by Lafe Lampton.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When he had proceeded a yard or two he stopped</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and looked about, trying to flash the light into the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">dark corners.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Both Jack and Lafe had a nervous feeling, that was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not fear, as they expected momentarily to see the au-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thor of those strange sounds bounce out of some cor-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ner and leap for the stairway, or for a window.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When nothing of the kind happened Jack went on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">again, holding up the lamp.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They crossed the room, discovering nothing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No one in here!" said Lafe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What's become of him?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack walked up to a pile of boards, from which some</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lew gymnastic apparatus was to be made by |he club</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">members.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He looked behind this; then swept his glance round</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the whole of the room.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">What surprised him as much as anything was that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not a thing within the gym seemed to have been dis-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">turbed. The Indian clubs, dumb-bells, leaping pad,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">chairs, in fact all the movable articles, were in place,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and appeared not to have been touched.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack was mystified.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Going to the nearest window opening upon the shed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">roof, he looked out On the shed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As before, Lafe followed him, and also looked out.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The night was rather dark, though stars were shin-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"There's no one on. the shed, I think," said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he called to the boys below;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You must have let the fellow get by you!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Not on your life we didn't!" came the answer.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, there's no one here." "</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, he's in there somewhere."</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack withdrew his head, and made another search</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of the gym, with the same result.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"There's nobody in here, and I know it!" Lafe de-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">clared, when they had gone over the whole upper floor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">three or four times.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You're right; there's no one here."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And nobody on the shed roof."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We couldn't see anyone there."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe whistled.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jiminy crickets, this is queer!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Too queer for anything," admitted Jack, feeling</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">undeniably foolish and nervous. "He must be either</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">here or on the shed roof, or else he got away."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He might be in the room below," Lafe suggested.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It seemed almost impossible that this could be so;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for the boys had been almost at the foot of the stairs</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">before the strange whacking and thumping in the gym</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had ceased.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nevertheless, Lafe lighted a lamp, and with this in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his hand he. went downstairs and began a search</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">through the old carriage shop.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack went to the window again, and informed the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boy of what Lafe was doing, and asked them to still</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">keep a sharp lookout.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">By and by he went himself down into the lower</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">room, carrying his lamp, but leaving another one</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lighted in the gymnasium.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The boys outside were in a state of mingled suspense</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and mystified curiosity. It seemed to them that any-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thing might happen now.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">On the lower floor were stored some old buggies,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wagons and broken-down carriages, together with</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rusty tires, splintered wheels, and the like.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack searched all over this lower floor, accompanied</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">by Lafe, and did not stop until it was certain no- one</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was hiding there.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he went to the door.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, this is a puzzler, fellows! There isn't a soul</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">upstairs nor down. There's no other place that chap</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="004" facs="004"/>
                <fw place="top">4 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">could have gone to; so he must have slipped out upon</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the shed roof. I'm going up to the gym and climb out</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on that roof. If he's there I'll find him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Look out that he don't tackle you and pitch you</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">off," Skeen warned.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He must be on that roof,v said Jack, "unless you</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">let him hop down and skip out here right under your</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">noses."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Not so much as a mouse hopped down'here!" Nat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kimball asserted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack went again into the gymnasium and climbed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">out on the shed roof.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He took with him a lantern, not willing to trust his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sight in that poor light; and with this means of illumi-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nation, he searched the shed roof from one end to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the other.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Nothing up here!" he shouted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels!" cried Skeen, who was now in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a nervous fever.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack retraced his way to the gym, and closed the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">window.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he went downstairs again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Fellows," he said, and his tone was serious, "where</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">did that chap go? It's a riddle, and I'm not good at</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">guessing."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Even yet the boys were not willing to believe that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the person, who had invaded the gym and made all</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that noise, could have escaped from the building; and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">they proposed a further search.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Other members of the club began to arrive, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">they joined in this search when they heard the strange</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and startling story.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Upstairs and downstairs, on the shed roof, under</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and in the old buggies and carriages, the club members</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">looked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When at length they gave it up as hopeless, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gathered in the gymnasium, with nearly every mem-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ber present now, some of them had passed from aston-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ishment to superstition.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Arlo Kilfoyle gave voice to what some of the others</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">were beginning to think, when he said:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It looks to me as if the old place must be haunted!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Haunted, your granny!" cried Nat Kimball.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, you believe in things as queer as that!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What? Tell me what?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Germs, for instance."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, that's science and common sense. Everybody!'</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">knows there are germs, and a lot of them; but whoever</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">saw a ghost?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Whoever saw a germ?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"They can't be seen, of course, without a micro-"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And ghosts can't be seen unless you're in a proper</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">condition to see them!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot laughed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We must have been in proper condition to heat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">them to-night!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's just it; you were!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"All of us?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Every one of you."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack laughed again, for Kilfoyle seemed to be in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sober earnest.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, that's all rot!" said Lafe Lampton.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He took out an apple, which he split open with his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hands, intending to give ^half to th£ boy who sat nexl</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then everyone laughed, when they saw the twc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">halves of the apple.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's rot, all right--that apple!" cried Skeen.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe opened the door of the stove, in which a fire</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was now roaring, and tossed the rotten apple into it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It's all rot about ghosts."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, then, Smarty, you explain what made those</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">noises!" said Kilfoyle. "There was some one in here!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">according to your own story; but when you came he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wasn't in here, and he had no chance to get out."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kilfoyle looked round; and then almost fell out of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his chair, as a strange sound seemed to come from the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">floor beneath him.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="005" facs="005"/>
                <fw place="top">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY 5</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was like a groan.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Say," cried Nat Kimball, anxiously and almost</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">angrily, "if any of you fellows have been practicing up</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on ventriloquism and are trying it here I don't think</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it's smart of you."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">All declared their innocence.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nat happened to think of ventriloquism, because, in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">addition to his jiu-jitsu studies, he had been poring</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">over some pamphlets that professed to explain the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">methods of the ventriloquist.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">All sat listening, Kilfoyle with his eyes wide open in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">glassy stare of fright.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nothing more was heard, however.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kilfoyle got up.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'm going home," he said. "You fellows can stay</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">here as long\as you please."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He arose and beat a retreat to the staifway, and then</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">drew back when he observed that the lower floor was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sunlighted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Taking a lamp, he descended with it; and, leaving</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it on the floor of the lower room, he departed from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the old carriage shop, to tell the story of the strange</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"manifestations."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The other boys remained, talking the thing over</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">seriously.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But the mystery was not to be solved by talk.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When, at a rather late hour for the club, whose</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">members tried to reach home early after a meeting,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">they had left the building and were proceeding up the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">street, their ears were again assailed by those mys-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">terious noises.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Whack! bang! Blub-bub-blub! Thump! bang!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">They ran back as quickly as they could; and again,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">while the outside of the shop was guarded, another</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">search was made.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This search resulted as before.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nothing could be found, and nothing further was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">heard.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">There were no evidences, the next morning, that the</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">carriage shop had been visited, except by the club</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">members, and not a thing could be discovered that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">would give the slightest clew to what appeared to be</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">an impenetrable mystery.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And, as a result, more than one aged woman and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">man in Cranford stood ready to declare that the old</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">carriage shop was haunted; and they told tales of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">strange happenings in the shop in days gone by, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">especially dilated on the fact that the man who bflilt</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the shop and ran it at first had fallen into the lake one</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">night and been drowned, and his body had never been</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">recovered.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A more than a ten-days sensation in Cranford</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">seemed to be promised.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER II.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">PRACTICE ON THE DIAMOND.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The call of spring was stirring in the blood of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boys of the high-school athletic club, as they gathered</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on the diamond, in the old fair grounds, where the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">athletic events had been pulled off in the recent tourna-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ment.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Signs of spring were becoming apparent.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The snow was gone, the lake and the rivers were</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">dear of ice, and robins were hopping about in search</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of worms, perking their heads and looking wisely at</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the passers-by.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Yet, in our changeable climate, winter might return</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">with a suddenness that would cause these signs to be</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">forgotten, and the land might be covered again with</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">snow.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But the high-school boys did not think this likely;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and as they stood about, and the ball was thrown from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">one to another, while bats were flourished, they began</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to talk of the trip into the woods, which they had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">planned should take place as soon as the weather was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fit.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"By hemlock, I know the fish air bitin'!" said Jubal</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="006" facs="006"/>
                <fw place="top">6 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Marlin, spreading his wide, good-humored Yankee</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mouth in a grin.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Marlin attended the high school only when he felt</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">like it, and that made him a very irregular student,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">indeed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Yet, as he could play baseball pretty well, and was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">eligible for membership in the high-school athletic</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">club, he had been chosen as one of the substitute play-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ers, and was on the diamond that day for the first prac-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tice work of the season.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen slapped a hand to his cheek.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels, spring is here, fellows!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">There's the first mosquito!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yeou got the first bite!" said Jubal. "I allow</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">yeou'll make a record when go fishin'."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I think I'd like a bite."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was Lafe Lampfon who spoke, and the inevitable</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">apple came out of his pocket.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"How long is that barrel of apples your folks bought</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">last fall going to last?" Jack Lightfoot asked, as Lafe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bit into his prize.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Barrel! We bought ten barrels last fall."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And you've eaten the most of them."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, you fellows helped."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He broke the apple in two and handed a half to the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boy nearest him, as was his. habit; then took another</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bite out of the portion he had reserved for himself.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"By gravy, I feel strong enough tew knock the cover</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">off'n that ole ball, this mornin'!" said Jubal, swinging</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his bat at an imaginary ball. "Just send it over here,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fellers, and see me paste it."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He swung the hat left-handed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You ought to be a good run-getter, Jube," Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">remarked. "A left-handed batter has an advantage</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">over a right-handed one. He is likely to trouble the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pitcher, in the first place; and then he has the advan-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tage of a fine start from the home plate after hitting the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ball, and if he is a good runner he will make first base</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">'twenty per cent, oftener than a right handed man."</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jube grinned in a pleased way.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We'll put you in the outfield," said Jack. "You</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a good thrower."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jube grinned again; and the ball being sent to him</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">by Bob Brewster, he proceeded to "knock the cover off</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of it" by lifting a high fly, which Ned Skeen caught</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">without trouble.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Judgment!" Skeen howled.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Out!" yelled Lafe Lampton, his mouth filled with</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">apple.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Give him another, Bob," said Jack, as the ball was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thrown to Brewster, "and let's see if he can land it in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the left field."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I can land it any old place," said Jube, with another</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">grin.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Crack!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">His bat struck the ball, and again he knocked a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">high fly, which Skeen again smothered.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels, baseball practice tingles my</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">heart all up!" said Skeen, as he sent the ball to Brew-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ster.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe threw down his apple core and got behind the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">batter.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot went down to the pitcher's box, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">taking the ball, sent in a twister.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Knock the cover off this!" he invited.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jubal, with a left-handed swing, drove at the ball</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">but it dipped downward as he struck, and he fanned</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the air.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He grinned, as before.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, that ain't fair! That didn't come straight."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Try this, then."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack threw another drop, but a slow one, this time.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jube struck at it before it reached the plate.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Judgment!" roared Ned Skeen, falling back on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the new green grass and kicking his heels in the air.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Two strikes!" said Bill Brewster, volunteering as</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">umpire.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yeou can't dew, that ag'in," Jubal declared.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="007" facs="007"/>
                <fw place="top">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY 7</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack threw another.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It came like a bullet, and twisted to the right, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">again Jubal threshed his club through the empty at-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mosphere.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Out! Three strikes and out!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Now, I'll give you an easy one," said Jack, "and I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">want you to try to bunt it. A left-handed batter has</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a good chance, if he can stop the ball with skill; he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">can, if he is quick, bunt the ball and be away from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the plate before it hits the ground. Now, look out;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ready!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He sent in an "easy one," but it was high, and Jubal</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">failed to get it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But he did better the next time, and bunting the ball</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">down in front of the plate, he was able to reach first.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You've got to look lively there, Lafe," Jack warned.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No time for apple eating."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe Lampton walked out leisurely, and as leiisurely</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">threw the ball down to the box.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But this isn't a real game," he urged.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No, it isn't--just practice; but if we're slovenly</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and slow in practice we'll be that way when we go</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">into a real game. Quickness, alertness and sureness--</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">those are the things that count."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nat Kimball took up the club and stepped into posi-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ion.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What's the best way to stand?" he asked, as he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">faced the pitcher.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That depends on the man," Jack answered. "Some</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">like to stand as close up to the plate as the rules will</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">allow; others stand away from it a little. There used</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to be a professional player on the Bostons who stood</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nearly three feet away from the plate, and he was a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">great batter; but he was a remarkable exception."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He was turning the ball round in his hands as he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">talked, and looking at Kimball.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's a pretty good position you've got now," he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said. "But remember one thing, you're to watch me.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">f I were pitching in a game I'd try to throw you just</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the kind of ball you weren't looking for; or, if I had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">found out what was the hardest ball for you to bat,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I might throw you that. If you keep your eyes well</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">peeled you can often detect a curve, just as it breaks in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">its course, and have time to land on the ball."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He threw, with a quick jerk, and the ball coming</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">straight, though with good speed, Kimball cracked it</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">out into left field.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Arlo Kilfoyle, who was out there, fumbled it, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">almost fell down, and Kimball took second.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kimball, on second, began to look for a chance to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">steal.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack spoke to him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"There's just one thing, Kimball, I want to call your</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">attention to now. When you hit the ball and get away</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for first, never look back to see where the ball has</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gone; judge that from the action of the first baseman.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">You slowed up, when you looked back, and you might</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">have been put out."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But I made second!" Kimball argued.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"True, you did, this time. But I'm giving you rules</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to cover your base running generally.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Thus the practice oh the diamond went on; and all</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the while Jack Lightfoot was carefully sizing up his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">men, and judging as best he could in what positions</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">they would be able to do their best work.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">All kinds of sports, and baseball especially, seemed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to come as a natural knack to Jack Lightfoot; yet no</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boy in Cranford had studied the game more closely, or</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">practiced more assiduously.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In addition to this he was a born leader, knowing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">how to get the best work put of those under him; and,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">though he had his failings, as most boys have, he had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">innumerable good qualities to offset them.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The entire time of the boys was not given, however,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to practice and the discussion of the rules and the fine</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">points of ball playing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They could not get out of their minds the strange</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">occurrences in the gymnasium the preceding evening.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="008" facs="008"/>
                <fw place="top">8 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, this talk that the gym is haunted by the ghost</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of that old fellow who was drowned, and who first</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">owned the building, is the worst kind of rot!" said</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe, emphasizing his belief by a wise shake of his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">head.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, I'd just like to meet the guy who is trying</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to be smart in that way," was the assertion of fighting</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul Messenger.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We'll watch for him to-night," said Jack. "I've</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">already spoken to Kennedy, and he's going to keep an</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">eye out down there, to see if he can discover anybody</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lurking round the building."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">None of the fellows, not even Arlo Kilfoyle, was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">willing to believe now that there was anything super-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">natural in the noises they had heard, strange as those</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">noises had been.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Daylight had strengthened Kilfoyle's nerves.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ghosts are never seen by daylight, and even the most</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">superstitious feels that he can defy them when the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sun is shining brightly over his head.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Still, fellows, the thing was awfully queer!" Nat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kimball asserted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels, queer was no name for it!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said Ned Skeen.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And everyone there could agree to that.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER III.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A PAIR OF PLOTTERS.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nicholas Flint, dark, sinister of features, with high</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cheek bones, and black eyes that glittered like those of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">an Apache, was making his way across lots, some dis-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tance above the diamond.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">His way lay between the old fair grounds, where</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the high-school boys were practicing, and the railway,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that ran from east to west through the town of Cran-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ford.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">From his higher elevation he could look down into</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the fair grounds and see the boys, as he had already</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">heard them.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As he looked, the black eyes glowed and snapped</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">with hidden fire.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint did not like Jack Lightfoot.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It will do me good to get a chance to punch the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">head off of that guy!" he muttered, standing in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">open lot and looking down at the pitcher's box, from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">which Jack was handing out those practice balls. "He</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thinks he's too smart for anything! Oh, I'll hammer</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">him!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint's particular grievance at this time was that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack had refused to let him substitute on the new</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">high-school nine.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He did not attend school much, but he fancied that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">this should not disqualify him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It did not, in truth, for Jube Marlin, who could not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">be called a regular school attendant, was on the list of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">substitutes.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">What disqualified Nicholas Flint, in Jack's estima-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tion, was his utter unreliability, his untruthfulness, his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">quarrelsome disposition, and the fact that, altogether</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he was about as unpromising a boy as could be chosen</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for he was no ball player, and likely never could be-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">come one.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">What Jack Lightfoot sought for, was good baseball</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">material; and while he was glad to have his friends on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the nine, if they were good players, he would not even</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">put a chum on, unless that boy could add strength to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the nine.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And, certainly, if he would not put on a friend who</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was a poor player, he would not use so wretched an</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">athlete as Nicholas Flint, just to please him and avoid</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his anger.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"When I get through with him he won't be able</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to lift his arm above his head, let alone pitch a ball,"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint threatened, mouthing away to himself in his rage</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">as he walked on. "Oh, I'll hammer him!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he stopped; for, coming to a little hollow</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">where the sun beat in warmly against a stone, he saw</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="009" facs="009"/>
                <fw place="top">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY. 9</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">lying there the one boy he was just then anxious to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">see --Bat Arnold.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Hello!" said Bat, looking up lazily, for the warm</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sunshine made him feel indolent.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick Flint glanced quickly around, and then dropped</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">as quickly into the cavity where Bat lay.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I've been watching the high-school crowd down</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">here," said Bat; then added, in an ironical way--"you</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fought to be on that nine!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick did not catch the irony in this; he thought the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">words were spoken in sober earnest.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I would have been, but for that puppy, Jack Light-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foot!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat laughed lazily.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, I mean it! I wanted to play substitute. You</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">know I can run!" continued Flint.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, you can run, all right!" admitted Bat, laughing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">again, when he remembered that he had once seen Nick</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">running like a sprinter from Kennedy, the night watch-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">man.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What are you laughing about? I don't see any-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thing funny."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I don't see anything funny--but you!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Me?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yes, it's funny that you should imagine for a min-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ute that Jack Lightfoot would let you sub. He'd never</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">do it. You don't belong in his crowd; you ain't fine-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">haired enough. You've got to be swell and away up,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you know; a nice little, clean little, honest little boy, to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">play with such a darling as Jack Lightfoot!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He spoke with a sneer; then laughed again, in a way</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to make Flint's dark cheeks flush.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jube Marlin isn't swell, or rich, or away up; and,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">when you come to that, Jack's mother hasn't got any</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">money much, that I ever heard of!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, well, you can be swell without money. Comb</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">your hair nice, you know, and get the girls to think</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you're it, and the ladies to speak sweet things about</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you, and you are all right. I know!"</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">There was little danger that the ladies of Cranford,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">or anyone else, would be likely to speak in very favor-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">able terms of Bat Arnold, if he did not mend his ways</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and his disposition; but Bat did not think of that.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint looked down upon the diamond, that flush on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his face, and his black eyes snapping.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he shoved a hand into his pocket.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When it came out it held a hundred dollars in green</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">backs.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold's eyes rounded, and he stared in amaze-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ment.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had never seen Flint with so much money, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">felt sure he had not come by it honestly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The sight of those bills almost frightened him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Where did you get that?" he asked, in awe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint counted out five ten-dollar bills, and threw</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">them to him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What do you want me to do with them?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"They're yours."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"To keep?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yes, to keep--perhaps."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Where'd you get 'em; that's what I want to know?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, don't look at 'em that way; they're not coun-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">terfeit!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But where did you get 'em "</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint took them again, and held them alluringly in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his hands.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"How would you like to have this fifty dollars, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fifty more on top of it?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A covetous look came into Bat's eyes, and he thrust</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">out his round, bullet head significantly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Try me," he said, at length. "What you got up</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">your sleeve?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint wadded the bills together.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I know of a feller who'll give that much, and more,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to have Jack Lightfoot done up."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Killed?" Bat gasped.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No, of course not."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What's he want done?"</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="010" facs="010"/>
                <fw place="top">10 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, if we thump the very old tat out of Lightfoot</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the feller I'm speaking of will be satisfied.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Is this chap a man?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yes, he's a man."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Why don't he do it himself, then?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's his business!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"See here, did somebody give you that money just</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to get you to whip Jack Lightfoot?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He wants him more than whipped; he wants him</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">used up."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What for?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's his business!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold looked incredulous.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'll bet I know who that man is," he said, finally.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'll bet you don't!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It's Prof. Sanderson."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint stuck his tongue in his cheek and winked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Go ahead with your guessin'."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I know it's Sanderson."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Would he take such a risk?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He don't like Jack."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But would he take such a risk? The people of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Cranford wouldn't stand for a thing like that."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"If they didn't know. Ah! come; it's Sanderson!""</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick Flint winked again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It's no difference to you, is it, who hands over the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">swag, if you get it?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold was silent again, thinking this over.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had discovered that Prof. Sanderson, of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Cranford Academy, did not like Jack Lightfoot.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Yet it did not seem to him that Sanderson would</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">be such a fool as to risk his position and his popularity</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">by such an undertaking as Nicholas Flint had outlined.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You won't say it's Sanderson?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I won't confess who it is. All I'll say is, that here</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">is a hundred dollars, and there's to be a hundred more,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">When Jack Lightfoot is put out of business for the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">season."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"For the season?"</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's what I said, didn't I? For the season! He</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wants to be made a subject for a doctor and a hos-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pital. Not any little cheap thrashing, but a regular</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hammering, that will simply half kill him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"So that he won't be in shape to lead his athletic</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">team this summer and beat the academy boys at base-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ball? Is that the ticket?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat was still thinking that the man who wanted this</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">done must be Prof. Sanderson, who would naturally</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not like to have Jack Lightfoot head a nine that would</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lay it over the nine from the academy.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'm not giving this thing away," said Nick Flint</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I've told you all you need to know."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Why didn't you take the contract, instead of com-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing to me with it? Then you'd had the whole two</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hundred."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint's Apache face flushed again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You knew you wasn't equal to the undertaking, I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">guess!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Think what you please," said Flint. "Do you want</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">into this thing with me, or not? I've told you all I'm</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">going to. Here's a hundred, and you can have half</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of it right now. When Jack is polished off in good</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">shape there's to be another hundred, and you can have</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">half of that."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold twisted uneasily on the grass. Plucking</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">one of the grass blades, he set it between his teeth</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and chewed at it reflectively.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Say," he said, suddenly, "is the feller that gave</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you that the one who kicked up that hullabaloo at</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lightfoot's gym last night?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Do you think Sanderson would have done that?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I hadn't thought so, no; but it came to me that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">maybe this millionaire that's throwin' his money round</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">so free might be the feller that kicked up the racket in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the gym."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nicholas Flint again stuck his tongue into his cheek</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and winked knowingly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Bat, what you don't know will never hurt you!"</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="011" facs="011"/>
                <fw place="top">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY. 11</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What do you mean by that?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That if you don't know too much, you'll not have</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to tell too much, if our game fals through and we</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">get caught. If anything happens, I'm a regular Know</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nothing? I never heard of any man, nor ghost in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gym, never saw any money, haven't the slightest</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">knowledge of Prof. Sanderson--don't know anything.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I simply join the Know Nothings, and keep my mouth</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">shut. You might be leaky; and that's why I'm not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">going to tell you any more than I've got to."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold did not like this plain speaking.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Can't you trust me?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Sure; I'm trusting you, when I stand ready to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hand over this fifty dollars to you!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You ought to tell me the whole thing," Bat in-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sisted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I won't. I'll tell you this, though. If I felt sure</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I could handle Jack Lightfoot alone I wouldn't have</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">come to you. I'm offering to divide with you to get</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">your help. Might's well be frank, you know!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold rose to his feet, as if angered; then,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thinking better of it, or longing too much for that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">money, he dropped down again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"How's this going to be done?" he asked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Are you ready to go into it with me? I want to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">know that first."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Maybe."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You haven't any cause to like Jack Lightfoot any</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">more than I have. He's done you mean, just as he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">has me. He thinks he's away above you, and looks</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">down on you; you're no better than the dirt under his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">feet, to him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He was appealing now to the baser feelings of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boy he was trying to overpersuade.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He didn't treat me bad, at the time of the tourna-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ment!" said Bat.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And another thing--you want the academy nine to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">win in the games that are being talked of for this</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">season. Knock Jack out, so that he can't play, and</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="02"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">can't lead his nine, and your fellows of the academy</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">will have a walk-over."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, we can beat those high-school scrubs, any-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">how!" Bat boasted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, you'll see."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jack didn't do such-a-much in the baseball games</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">last season."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He batted your fellows out of the box, in the next</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to the last game; and in the last game he simply struck</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you out like one--two--three. I was there, and I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">saw it"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, he can't do it again! He's got a nine that will</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">go to pieces, all right, all right!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nicholas Flint began to lose his patience. He stuck</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the money into his pocket.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"All right," he said If you don't want that hun-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">dred dollars I can find a fellow who does. And if</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you say anything of what I've said to you about it,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">why, then, you and I will mix, and I'll pound your face</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">off."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold chewed hard on the grass blade, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ignored this.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He wanted that hundred dollars.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You haven't told me how this thing is to be done?"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he reminded.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, I'll tell you. Lightfoot and his friends are</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">going on an outing into the woods, down by Simm's</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hole. We'll lay for him down there."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Is that, the only plan you've got?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I've got some other things in my mind, but I'm</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">going out to Simm's Hole first and take a look around</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">before I'm ready to say what they are. Does that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">satisfy you?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold did not answer at once.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The good and the bad in him were struggling for</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">supremacy.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He wanted that money, but he did not like the means</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that were proposed to enable him to get it; and, worse</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="012" facs="012"/>
                <fw place="top">12 ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">than that, he did not want to do anything that might</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">get him into trouble with the officers of the law.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I feel sure of one thing!" he declared.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What is it?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"For all that you won't say it, I'll bet Prof. San-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">derson is back of this thing, and that he knows all</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">about that monkey business in the gym last night.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">That was done to scare Lightfoot's crowd. I don't see</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">what it amounts to, though. What does it accomplish,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">if they do get frightened by that?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick Flint again winked, and thrust his tongue</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">knowingly into his cheek.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Bat, what you don't know will never hurt you!" he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And he would explain no further.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Will you go into it?" he demanded, finally.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Ye-yes, I think I will; but I'll tell you to-night."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You never had a chance to make a hundred dollars</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">so easy," Flint urged. "Make up your mind quick.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I'm going down to Simm's Hole this afternoon, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">when I get back I must have an answer. If you don't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">want the hundred dollars, I know of a fellow who'll</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">be glad to finger it, and do what I want done."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER IV.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A REQUEST.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">One of the places in which Jack Lightfoot loved to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">work and to study was the shed room, at home.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was back of the house, and connected with it, so</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that it was a part of the building.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Being warmed by a good stove in winter; there Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had his books, his tools and workbench, and some</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gymnastic apparatus, which he had used industriously</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">long before the gift of Norwell Strawn m3.de the upper</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">floor of the old carriage shop into a gymnasium.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Here came Tom Lightfoot, Jack's cousin, Lafe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lampton, and others of Jack's friends, to talk and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">while away spare hours, and to study, or use the work-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bench and the tools.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack's'friends found the shed room a pleasant pla</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">whether in summer or in winter, and Jack Lightfc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pleasant company a«d a stanch friend at all times!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe Lampton chanced tp be in the shed room on t</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">particular afternoon, talking with Jack of the pract</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">work of the morning, and of the mysterious happ&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ings in the gymnasium the night before.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Suddenly a man came round the neat, white-pain-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">house, having admitted himself into the yard by •</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">front gate, and, advancing to the door of the si</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">room, knocked on it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe got up and opened the door.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The man who stood there was a singular characl</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">known throughout the county as Deaf Peleg. I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">name was Peleg Brown.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab/>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="01" facs="01"/>
                <fw place="top">1</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab> </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He lived in a cabin not far from Simm's Hole, e</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">made his living, such as it was, by a little garden:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and a good deal of hunting and fishing, with oc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sional trapping in the fall and winter.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg stood hesitating in the doorway, then ca</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">into the shed room.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No use to ask him what he wants," said Lafe;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">so deaf he couldn't hear thunder."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg walked straight across to the writing desk</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the further end of the room, where the window g;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a good light and a bookshelf showed its volumes; 1</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">stooping over the desk began to \frrite on some pa</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he found there.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Thus bent over and scribbling away, he present©</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">queer figure.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Though the day had been warm, he was muffled</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had on an overcoat, a red woolen "comforter'' rot</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his neck, and his cap pulled down over his ears.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He wore no more beard than an Indian, his sn</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">face had a cunning look, something like that of a f</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and his little eyes seemed to want to hide themselves</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">their deep sockets,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">\</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In addition, Peleg was toothless; and,7 though</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">could not speak, for he was dumb as well as deaf,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="013" facs="013"/>
                <fw place="top">13</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">unched his toothless jaws together, as if he were</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ring to say something, whenever he was communi-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">iting with anyone, either by signs or written words.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Having scribbled for some time at the writing desk,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">kleg came hack toward Jack Lightfoot, working"*his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">l\vs as he came, and then thrust out the paper he had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ritten.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Both Jack and Lafe read it, and it was a singular</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">id startling communication.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I Here it is, just as old Peleg wrote it:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">|"Twict I have seen a ghost at my house. Night</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fefore last he came ahd stud by my bed. Last night</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">te come again. I was by my pig pen, fcedin' my</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jig: and he come and stud by the corner of the pen."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">♦</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jiminy crickets!" said Lafe Lampton.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack took the paper and wrote:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">PTell us more. What did he look like?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then Peleg wrote:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">PHe was tall; hadn't any head nor any neck, but</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ent straight up like a stovepipe from his shoulders."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jiminy crickets!" said Lafe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Again Jack wrote.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">PWhat did he do?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Nothing," was the answer.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">?Nice ghost," said Lafe, commenting.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ack wrote:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[ %</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fDid you see him good; and what do you want</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">to do?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'Seen him all right," wrote Peleg, "and I want you</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">come out and see him, too, to-night, or soon's you</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">i."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'Do you believe in ghosts?" Jack asked, writing</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">i question.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I do, hjmn' seen one; you come out and take a</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">&gt;k; and if it is a man help me trap him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then he isn't sure that it is a ghost," said Lafe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">e isn't as bfg a fool as he looks."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">5eleg wrote other things, but they did not add to the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ire of information already furnished.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack wrote once more:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We're coming out to Simm's Hole, to camp and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fish. I'll hurry the trip, so that we can get to see</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">your ghost."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then Peleg departed, and the boys sat down to talk</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it over.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">%</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'm getting all balled up," Lafe acknowledged; and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he took out an apple and set his teeth in it, as if fancy-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing that setting his jaws to working would help to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">limber up the machinery of his mind.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What do you think about it?" he asked, not able</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to make any good- guess himself.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I don't know what to think."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Is there any connection between the 'ghost' Peleg</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">says he saw out there, and the noise we heard in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gym last night ?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"It's queer that Peleg came to me," said Jack; "or,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rather, came to us, here in this room. Why didn't he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">go to Kennedy, the constable ?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Perhaps he did; we didn't ask him about that."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'T didn't think of it then; but we'll find out if he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">went to Kennedy." •</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"t)f course this ghost business is all rot!" said Lafe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Of course."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Somebody's working a trick. Or it may be one</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">person here, and another out there at Simm's Hole."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We'll watch the gym to-night," said Jack. "If</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">we can get sight of the fellow who is cutting up per-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">haps we'll learn more. But, anyway, we've planned to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">go to Simm's Hole."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot came in, and as the written state-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ments of the queer deaf mute had been saved, they</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">were shown to him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom had not been at the gymnasium the preceding</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">night, but he had heard of the mysterious invader and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the strange sounds made.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Every person in Cranford had heard these facts.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom sniffed contemptuously.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I think this whole business, at the gym and down</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="014" facs="014"/>
                <fw place="top">14</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">at Simm's Hole, is just the work of kids, who are</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">trying to have what they'd call fun."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Tom," said Lafe, speaking seriously, "you weren't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">at the gym last night! The kid who made that racket</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">there must have been a mighty little fellow, to have</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">got out past us without our seeing him, or to have re-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mained in there without our discovering him."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You'd have seen him, probably, if he came out,"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom admitted. "So it's certain he stayed in there.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">There are a lot of old holes in and under those car-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">riages and buggies."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We looked everywhere."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">''Everywhere but in the right place. Why, you</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">don't mean to claim that he was neither there nor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">went away? If he didn't get out past you, where</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">could he have been but in the gym? Don't slip a cog</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">-and begin to talk silly!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yes, it does sound silly!" Lafe acknowledged.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But I wish you'd been there!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We're going to watch for him to-night," said</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'll go with you," Tom volunteered.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER V.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A WARNING.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack and Tom Lightfoot, Lafe Lampton and nearly</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">every member of the athletic club of the high school</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">spent several hours that evening in watching the old</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">carriage shop.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They first ascertained that no one was in it or about</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it; and then, hiding out in the darkness, they tried</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to make sure that no one came near it, or that if anyone</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">came, his identity should be made known.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot was a student at the academy, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on the nine that was expected to play against Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lightfoot's high-school team that summer.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nevertheless, as Jack's cousin, and having a warm</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">regard not only for Jack, but for other members of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his team, Tom Lightfoot was willing to assist in try-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">P .</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing to discover the "ghost" that was troubling th</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">quiet of the high-school boys' gymnasium.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The suggestion, lightly made by some one, that th</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">academy fellows were at the bottom of it he repudiate-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rattier warmly; so that it was not brought up agai:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that night.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">While the boys lay out in the gloom, with ever</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sense on the alert, there came a repetition of the sound</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">heard the night before:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Whack! Bang! Blub-rub-bub! Whack! Bang</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot laid his hand on the shoulder of hi</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cousin Jack, as the two were lying close together.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"There it is I" said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Some one is in there now, all right," said Torr</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">starting up. "Keep the place surrounded, and we'll sd</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">who it is, and what he's doing."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The cordon of watchers guarded the carriage shof</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">so that no one could leave it or approach it without di$</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">covery; while Tom, Jack and Lafe Lampton, enterq</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the building, lighted lamps, and made a search.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This night they did not find everything upstairs ij</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">such perfect order. The leaping pad had been turne</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">over, and the Indiaif clubs were at the other side c</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the room from the place where they were usually kep</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No ghost here!" Tom announced.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And nothing else," said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It seemed true.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">No one could be found on the upper floor, dow</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">below, or out on the shed roof; and there were r</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">other places to look.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot began to feel queer, himself.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"This rather gets me, fellows," he admitted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We thought it would," said Lafe, almost ma</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ciously. "Yet I remember you said that ?f the fellq</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">didn't get out he was still in. He hasn't got out; ai</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">if he's still in, I'd be glad to have you show me whe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he is."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom scratched his head, as he went downstairs</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As they came out of the doorway there was an e</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="015" facs="015"/>
                <fw place="top">15</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab> </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He saw a small stone on the floor, with a paper</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wrapped about it and tied there with a string.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">That was the object that had come through the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">window.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">On removing the string and the paper, Jack found</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a communication.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It had not been written; but, to conceal the identity</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of the' one sending it, letters and words had been cut</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">from newspapers and pasted together into sentences,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thus:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"DO not Go tO Simm's hole. YOU Will be IN dan-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ger. take my ADVICE and stay AWAY. St&amp;y</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Away. THIS is a WARNING, i KNOW what I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">am TALKing about. STAY AWAY."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">\</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Again Jack went to the window and looked out.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Who could have thrown this through the window,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and what danger can there be in going to Simm's</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hole?" was his thought.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He turned the paper^over and looked at the back,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">which was blank.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Again he went to the window.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">At first he was disposed to go downstairs and tell</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his mother what had happened.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No use to disturb her," was his second; thought.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"In the morning will do as well."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He did not go to bed again for some time.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The shattered glass lay on the floor. This he picked</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">up carefully; and to keep out the chill wind that came</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">through the broken pane he stuffed some clothing in it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Think as he would, he could come to but one con-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">clusion ; arrd that connected the "danger" with the deaf</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mute.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">%</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Peleg is a queer old duck, and if this warning is</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">anything more than a joke it must refer to something</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he is up to. That ghost story of his may have been</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a lie."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Of course Jack Lightfoot had never suspected that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg Brown had seen a ghost; but he was willing to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">believe that the deaf mute had really beheld some-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Idamation and a cry of excitement; then Ned Skeen</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">exclaimed:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">f We've got some one!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, cut it out!" came in the voice of Bat Arnold.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">p'I just came down here to see if you fellows had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">■discovered anything. I heard uptown that you was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">watchin* the gym to-night."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">\</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You didn't drop off the shed roof?" asked Jack,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">flashing a match and looking Bat in the face.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Off the shed roof? Nixy. I came right down</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ihis street, and if your crowd hadn't been staring at</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the shop they'd have seen me."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">! A dozen boys stood ready ter declare that Bat had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not dropped from the shed roof, though his presence</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ihere had somewhat surprisecf them, for they had not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">heard his approach.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Released, Bat went uptown,, and the watch was re-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">«</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sumed.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">IBut nothing came of it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The mystery was too deep for easy solution, and the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">oys went home at last, baffled, though some of them</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ung round the carriage shop until nearly midnight.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot did not believe in late hours, and</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">rent home early, yet he could not sleep, because of</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">orrying over the mystery.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He wondered if it had any connection with the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ingular message brought by the deaf mute.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We'll hurry up that outing to Simm's Hole," was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his conclusion.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">IT.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">r. As if his decision had brought it, there was a crash</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">St feis window--the crash of a breaking pane--and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">si something fell with a thump on the .floor.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">'■ Jack was out of bed instantly.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">T He ran to the shattered window, but saw no one;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">| which was not strange, for the night was cloudy, nor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I didjie hear the sound of footsteps.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tfembling and startled, he struck a match and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^lighted his lamp.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">l6</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thing, which his superstitious imagination 'had taken</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for such.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Now he doubted even that; and was almost disposed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to think, if the warning were not a practical joke, that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg was up to some mischief, which the one sending</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the warning wished to caution him against.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Why couldn't he have said what it was? This</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thing of throwing a stone through my window is</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sneaking, of itself. It broke the window; and doesn't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tell me anything, more than that there is danger.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">What kind of danger, and from whom ?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack went to bed pondering these questions, and fell</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">asleep before he had arrived at any conclusion.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER VI.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">IN THE WaODS.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"In the good ojd summer time,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In the good old summer time,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Rambling down a shady lane</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With your Baby jVJjne!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">You hold her l^and, and-"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Cut it out!" said Lafe Lampton, speaking to Nat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Kimball, "the sweet warbler of Simm's Hole," as the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boys called him ; "this-isn't summer time--it's spring!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">""And we didn't think he'd spring that on us!" added</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack had disregarded the warning so strangely sent</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">him, and was at Simm's Hole, with his friends.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THe day was glorious; not a fleck of cloud in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">azure sky, a warm wind, and the budding trees send-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing out woodsy odors.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Simm's Hole lay to the westward of tKfe town of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Cranford, two or three milps distant.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Laurel River, heading up in the hills, flowed into the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">western end of Cranford Lake, which was a somewhat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">oblong body of water, set between a wild woodland on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">one sjdfe^and the level country containing the town</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of Cranford and many fine farms on the other.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Laurel River, flowing into Cranford Lake, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Malapan River, flowing out of it at the other end,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">might have been considered in a sense as one stream</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">flowing from the timbered hills through the lake an</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on to- the sea; but they were two rivers, to the Cra</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ford people, and bore separate names.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Malapan River, emptying into the sea; was a tid</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">channel.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Laurel River, emptying into the lake, was fresh, ar</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was fed by some famous trout streams.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Simm's Hole was a deep cavity in the bed of Laur</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">River, a few hundred yards above the upper end j</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the lake.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">All about Simm's Hole lay heavy woodlands, whii</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in some places became a wild tangle.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Just above Simm's Hole, and really hanging or</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it, or rather projecting into it, was an old dam.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This dam was much broken. In places it stood r</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and over these places the water tumbled with a ro</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">♦</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and a beautiful waterfall effect.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In the broken places there were here and there pr</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jecting sticks of timber, that thrust themselves upwa</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and whipped at the water like saws.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Swinging back and forth, they sometimes threw! t</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">water into spurting jets, which glistened brightly</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the sunlight.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">At one end of the dam, and built out upon it, w</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a tumble-down cabin, almost in ruins now.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg Brown, the deaf-mute, had lived there a lc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">time, and had put up the cabin in that queer pla1</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that he might be right at the fishing ground he lov«</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">without having to take the trouble even to walk to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg s present home lay further up the stream.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had abandoned the old cabin, that hung a.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">swayed at one end of the dam, because of a flex</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">which came suddenly one night, and rising into &lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cabin gave him the fright of his life.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">• Pe]eg, when that water rose, threatening to w£</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">him from his bed, climbed out on the cabin roof; 3</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">there some people passing in the morning discovei</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">him, sitting astride the ridge pole, making signs and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">forking his toothless jaws.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg bad been on that roof for hours, unable to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">sound, and expecting every minute that the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">oukl be carried away.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ook no chances with the treacherous spring</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">f Laurel Riven, after t!hat</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">he old cabin made a famous plate for the boys</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">me to catnp at Simm's Hole ; and often (hey sat</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">oorway, or hung out of its window, with their</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">lines whipping the river below in the "hole."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">better spot than the vicinity of Simm's Hole</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">have been chosen for a boys' camp; and here</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">spring came fishing and camping parties from</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">vn of Cranford, and from other points more re-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lighti'oot and his friends had brought up a</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">^ *• 9</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">bnt, and a complete camping outfit, with cooking</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Is. and a supply of food.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the tent stood deserted. Some of the boys, Jack</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">| of the number, had not even slept in it the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[us night, but had lain out under the trees, with</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">rering but their blankets, for the ground was</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">jry-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ie Lampton was the self-appointed cook of the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">not because he liked so much to cook, but be-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[he liked to keep close to the eatables, and while</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">pg he could satisfy his palate by tasting the vari-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">lishes he was preparing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Dking was really the only work t(iat Laf£ Lamp-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">loroughly enjoyed; and he could hardly under-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">why all the other boys had not clamored for</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">bsition.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">was now stirring something in an iron pot that</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">|d hung on a tripod over a fire out of doors.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ie blue smoke drifting up through the yet leafless</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ihes toward the bluer sky, and Lafe stirring, and</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[and then tasting, made a picture of contentment,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">with the other boys standing or lying about in various</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">attitudes of lazy enjoyment.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This was the situation, when Nat Kimball, carried</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">siway by the spirit of coming summer, beganA to pipe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">out that old chestnut, "The Good Old Summer Time."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Hit him with a brick, if he tries to sing it again!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">grunted Bob Brewster, who would never have heaved</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a brick at anyone, except under the. severest provoca-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tion.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, say, I'm too lazy for anything!" declared Tom</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lightfoot, who, because he was Jack's cousin, was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">there, though he belonged with the academy crowd.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But then Tom was a royal good fellow, who was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">welcomed anywhere.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen began to sing:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">■"Qh, the spring is a finer time</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Than the good old summer time j.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lying in the shady woods--"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, you don't need to be in the woods, to enable</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you to do thaf!" Nat Kimball declared.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Skeen looked at him reproachfully.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Isn't a fellow to be allowed to sing anything?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Not when he doesn't know how."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Haw, h^w!" laughed Jube Marlin, the wide-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mouthed Yankee.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Stepping back, to avoid the kick which Skeen de-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">livered as a jocular return, Nat Kimball sat down sud</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">denly, and in trying to save himself from the fall</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">plowed his fingers into the soft earth.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Now Kimball has got germs," chirged Arlo Kil-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foyle. "He always finds germs whenever he puts his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hands on the ground."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Well, if I do believe irt germs, I don't believe in</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">l</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ghosts!" Nat retorted. "You'd better go away back</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and sit down! A fellow that's queer enough to be-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lieve in ghosts shouldn't try to poke fun at anybody</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">else."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I don't know that there are any ghosts, and I don't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">know that there aren't," said Kilfoyle; "but you ex-</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="018" facs="018"/>
                <fw place="top">18</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">plain that business at the gym, will you? You can't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">do it."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Oh, gee! here's a nasty worm crawling over me!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cried Kimball, knocking it away with a look of disgust.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot began to sing :</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Light is the breeze in the treetops astir,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Fragrant the breath of the hemlock and fir;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bright is the sky as the eyes that we love,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Sweeter the brook song than note of the dove..</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen, who had been called down for his sing-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing, yet fancied he could sing, and had a real gift for</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hasty parody, cut in:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Kilfoyle sees spirits, and Kimball finds germs;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When there are no germs he is fighting with worms;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He. bats them, and cuffs them, and, oh! how he squirms I</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Cut it out!*' Kimball commanded, sharply.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tom Lightfoot continued:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Bowers of beauty and vistas so fair;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Far, far behind us each sorrow and care 1</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lighter our thoughts than the branches that swing,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Joyous our hearts as the birds on the wing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the woods."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Again Ned Skeen broke in, 'Tike a musical sea gull,"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">some of the fellows^ claimed;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Catching fresh colds that will make us all sneeze,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bored by mosquitoes and bitten by fleas;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Snakes for our playmates, and ants for our fare--</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tell uje, oh, tell me, who wouldn't be there?</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">• Deep( in the woods,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Deep in the wtfods."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Fellows, there are fleas here, or ants, or something,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and a lot of them," said Kimball, jumping up and be-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ginning to scratch his legs.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Pshaw, those are just germs; you got them off the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ground!'' declared Kilfoyle.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You'll see a ghost, or something, if I punch your</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">head!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jhck Lightfoot began to squirm; he had been lying</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">at his ease; under one of the trees, enjoying the jok-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing and the quick repartee: now he, too, got up.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The warm sunshine was bringing out various forms</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of insect life, but the ants predominated; they J</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the big, black, hungry variety, with jaws like J</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack brushed away the ants that troubled hq]</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">found a new seat; while the boys began to taljJ</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">insect life of the woods.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jirh Bright, whose qne great ambition wasJ</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">come an actor, leaped to' his fee£ and stretche^J</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hands with a stagy air:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Go to the ant, thou sluggard!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He declaimed this; then started on somethal</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"My name is Norval 1 On the Grampian</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">father feeds his flock. A worthy swain-----</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Stop! stop!" said Skeen, the little joker;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not getting that right!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Why isn't it right, me lord?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Because it isn't."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jim Bright laid his hand on his'heart an</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">■_/. • »</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Will Your Muchness be kind enough to s</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the right way?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Sure r</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen sprang to his feet. --</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Hear tne!" he cried, facing the other b</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">throwing- himself into the stagy attitude ass</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bright. "This is the way that oratorical geit</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">school readers should be delivered."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He* squared his shoulders.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"My name is Norval, on the Grampian Hil</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">father feeds his flock a worthy swain!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"A swain is a man," said Bright.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Sure !"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And your father feeds him to his flock?"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Footsteps were heard behind him, and there can</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">interruption, in the form of the deaf-mute, Peleg</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had some fish, which he delivered to Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foot, as a present for the boys; and then took out</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of paper.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack read aloud the words written on it by</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I seen the ghost again last night, right by this</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="019" facs="019"/>
                <fw place="top">19</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ime out of the old cabin. I never seen anything</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">1"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'hat do you say to. that ?' said Kilfoyle, alifiost</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">phantly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">say if that ghost comes fooling round the dam</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">vening I'll put him on my hook and catch a trout</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">him," was the irreverent response of Bill Brew-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">lore Releg turned away, the rattle of a cart was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and Jerry Mulligan, the warm friend of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">school boys, came into view along the woodsy</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">frith his horse and his cart, bringing some things</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">om the town for the camp.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">hurrool" he cried, swinging; his cap wften he saw</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nt and the camp. "I think, begorra, that I'll lay</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jrruk fer thief rist av the week and play lazy, too.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tis worrukin' all the toime makes a man a dull b'y."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">" 'All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy,' you</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nean," cried Kimball.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Jack was niver a dull boy!" said the humorous</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rish lad.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You didn't get it right, either of you," cried Skeen.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">This is the way. it goes: All play and no work,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nakes a boy a poor shirk!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">'Jack Lightfoot clapped his hands.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Skeeny, that's tKe best thing you've got up this</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">norning.!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You overlook my' poetry'," said Skeen.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack took the piece of paper which held Peleg's mes-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a?e, and wrote on it for the' deaf-mute:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">»</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"All riglpt; thank you for the information. We'll</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">eeP a sharp watch for that ghost to-night. And we</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lank you for thd'fish."'</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then Peleg went' away; and Jerry, hitching his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">orse, forgot for the time that he was a hard-working</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ut driver, and became as much .of a rollicking boy</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">5 any there;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER VII.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALONG THE STREAMS.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Whipping the trout streams that made down from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the hills into Laurel River furnisl^d some of the finest</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Sport the boys could desire.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">To throw the fly out oh the surface of the whirling</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">water, and let it drift down, taking care to keep even</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">youi; shadow from being seen by the wary fish that lie</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">under the edge of some rock or in a dark hole, is no</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">easy accomplishment.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">To throw, aritl throw again; to wade, and creep; to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">quiver with expectation; and then, in almost an unex-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pected mpment, to have the trout rise to the fly!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">After that, the singing df the reel; and the careful</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">work.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ho, there! Careful, careful; he'll break your tackle,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">or get away!' CarefulJ</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">To see the beautiful fish throw himself in a shining</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">leap clear out of the water; to feel the pull and tug;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to reel in; and then to have him go plunging, with the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">reel singing again!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Is there anything finer in the way of sport, for either</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">man or boy ?</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">There may be, yet it is doubtful.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The cool wind of spring blowing in your face, the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tang of spring in the air, the spirit of spring throbbing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and leaping in your veins, swelling your heart; the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">song of the racing brook in your ears, and the song of-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the breeze in the trees above your head, while the sun</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">shines brightly, and the air is filled with a thousand</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">odors, and n. thousand signs of new and budding life&gt;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">All this is yours, while you play the gamy trout,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and your reel sings.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Now you work him in nearer to the shore. He is</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">well exhausted by this tirr^e, but still game; and he de-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">serves well of you, for he made a fine, even a glorious,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fight</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He comes in sulking, perhaps; or, with a fresh acces-</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="020" facs="020"/>
                <fw place="top">20</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">sion of courage and strength, he strikes again for the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">black shadows in the stream, or in the pool.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">. Then, when at last you have him near the shore, you</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">must still use your utmost skill.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The landing net now, and more careful work; then</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">you lift him out of his element, and he is yours!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With such pleasure as this, Jack Lightfoot and his</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">boy comrades failed to remember the "ghost" that had</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">troubled the-gym, forgot all about the "ghost" seen</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">more than once by old Peleg; and neglected, or disre-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">garded, the warning message that had^come crashing</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">through Jack Lightfoot's chamber window at home.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But at night, when they came in tired, yet glowing,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">with innumerable stories to tell of the fish "th&amp;y didn't</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">get," of the many trout that' got away, bigger, far</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">bigger, than the ones caught; and they sat down be-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fore the tent in the gathering darkness, to sample the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fish, done to a turn by Lafe Lampton, the talk turned</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">frequently to the mystery of the gym, and to the ghost</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">that had stood in the door of Peleg's old cabin, and</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">had walked the broken dam before that door.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Apparently this ghost knew that a party of skeptical,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">rollicking young rovers was camped near the shore at</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Simm's Hole, and were so lacking in a proper spirit</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">of revecence that they would not have hesitated to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">take the said ghost by the collar, presuming that he</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">wore one, and chuck him into the water, just to serve</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">him right for night walking.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">So the ghost kept away.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But the fun and the sport were fast and furious, yet</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">of a perfectly harmless and jovial kind; the sort of</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fun. that never yet injured any boy, or made him less</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">manly when he became a man.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg came in, the second evening, to ask by means</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">of signs if the "ghost" had walked as yet.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Receiving an answer in the negative, he drew out</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">his writing pad and a pencil and began to write.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Usually, when Peleg did that, something interest-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing might be expected.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This was what he wrote, on the evening in question</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"In Simm's Hole lives the hermit trout. I hookec</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hint 'once, but he broke my pole and my line, and go</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">away from me; and high about drowned me. Mavb&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you catch him; I never could, except that one time, anc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">then I didn't land him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack read this aloud to the' boys, while Peleg lookec</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on, smiling and working his hairless, toothless jaws. 1</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He was still dressed as if he expected an early re-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">turn of winter, with a big coat on, and that "com-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">forter" round his thin neck; but he had discarded his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">woolen mittens, and no longer pulled his cap dowr</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">over his ears.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack wAte:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Where had a fellow better fish, to get him ?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg answered:</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Right before the cabin door; right out in front</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He hangs round under the logl of the old dam; ana</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">onct I seen him rise there, and snap a fly off'n the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">water, when the fly dropped down on the water. Ha</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was a whopper--nigh about big as a sturgeon, 1</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">thought. He's been there ten year, I guess; and if</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">you git him, you git a whale."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's a whale of a lie," said Ned Skeen, when</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">this was read.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"All right; we'll try for him," Jack wrote.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And Peleg, when he had read this, worked his hairj</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">less jaws again, and smiled.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack wrote many questions on Peleg's pad that even!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing, some of them about the "ghost"; and Peleg ani</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">swered, to the best of his ability.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He never saw any ghost there, and he never hooked</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">any such trout," Skeen persisted. "He's stringing us</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and's been stringing us from the first."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Begorra, I'll take his string to-morry, and thrj</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mesilf fer that fish!" said Jerry, who still lingered</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">unable to leave the joys of the camp at Simm's Hole</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">• • • f' ' • * 1</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Take his string? Oh, yes; the string he's string</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing us withl Wowl' Jerry, I'll duck you in the hol&gt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="021" facs="021"/>
                <fw place="top">21</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fchat, first chance I get; and that will give you an</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">prtunity to catch that whale with your hands!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ferry grinned.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He might dhrowned me, av he's as big as Pelig</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ir .</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">]ore than one of the boys believed that Peleg was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">inging" them, both about the fish and" with regard</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">le "ghost."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I '</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hey paid so little attention to his stories of the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in, that they went to sleep that night as usual,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">d in their blankets, und^r the trees; and were deep</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">e land of dreams, whe^Jerry, himself awake, sud-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">y aroused them.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I •</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">\''hoosh!" he whispered. "An' phat the divvil is</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">now, I wanty know ?"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">is hand touched Jack Lightfoot.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pk, aroused on the instant, lifted his head,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">e moonlight had come again, after many nights</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">l&amp;rkness, and it glanced whitely across Simm's</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">B, and lighted up the old cabin and the broken dam.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">B the dam near the cab?n, sitting as if looking</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">n into the stream, holding a fishing pole, too, was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bgmge, tall figure, clad in something that looked</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">1st white in the moonbeams.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">■tn shwearin' that's the ghost, though I niver seen</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lefure!" whispered Jerry.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ik rolled over and touched Tom and Lafe, whis-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">k their names, to arouse them.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">■fe threw up his hands, with an exclamation that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lied very loud in that deep stillness.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Iparently it reached the strange form sitting on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I'oken dam, for the figure rose up suddenly, stand-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hdien erect, to an enormous height, and straight as</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hjvepipe" from waist to head, as Peleg iftd re-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">lit thus stood up, it seemed to slip, without mo-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">to melt as it were, into the very walls of the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then it was gone, without a sound.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The camp had been aroused by Lampton's exclama -</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tion.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"The ghost!" said Jack. "Whatever it was, man</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">or spirit, it went into that cabin. Come on, and we'll</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">'find it."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He did not stop to dress, but with his blanket drawn</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">about him, ran toward the dam and the cabin, which</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">were but a few yards away.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The other boys followed hot at his heels, clad in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">same way; and with them came Jerry, who had been</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the one to discover the "ghost."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But when the dam and the cabin were gained they</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">could find nothing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A search of the interior resulted in the same way.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Apparently no man had been in the cabin or on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the dam. No fishing pole could be found, no wet</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tracks--nothing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot and his companions were puzzled.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Niver a ghost was that!" said Jerry, decidedly, as</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he hunted through the cabin.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What became of him, then," Kilfoyle asked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He made a shneak into the woods, do ye' see! He</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">could 'ave done ut. He could have jomped aff the dam</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">here, and scooted into the thimber, and the bushes</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">would soon hicie him. I'm bettin' me owld hat ut was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that way."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was the best theory that could be conjured up, yet</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">not entirely satisfying; and Jack and the others re-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">turned to the camp and to their blankets, to lie awake</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a long time, thinking it over.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER VIII.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE ATTACK.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The next morning, when Jack awoke, he saw Nich-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">olas Flint sitting on the dam, while Bat Arnold was</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">just coming out of the woods.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Hello!" Jack called, rolling out of his blankets, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in so doing, and in calling out that way, waking the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Other members of the camping party.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="023" facs="023"/>
                <fw place="top">23</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">all-sports library.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But the sun was rising, arid the time had come for</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">theth to arise, so Jack did not mind thatT</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick Flint did not appear to notice Jack's civil</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">salute.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He's no good,v Lafe grunted, when he saw Flint.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What's he doing up here, while we're in camp? We</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">don't want him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Perhaps he doesn't want us," remarked Jack, easily.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He seems to have been first on the dani, this morn</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">• „ &gt;1</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Having dressed, ..he walked out to the dam.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Hello, Flint!" he said again; then added: "You</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">didn't see anything of a ghost round here, early chfs</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">morning?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I haven't lost any ghosts," Flint answered, surlily.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">»</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"But we're hunting one. He was sitting last night</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">right where you are sitting now, and he seemed to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">slide into the door there. We couldn't find him;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">though we came over and looked around."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Huh!" Flint grunted, skeptically.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold came up, smoking a cigarette.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Mornin' I" he growled.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He did not look at Jack, but kept the visor of his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cap pulled down over his eyes.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"The fishing is great," said Jack. "We've--been up</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and down all of the creeks, and the trout are biting</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fine. Perhaps yotl'd like to sample some that we've</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">caught; we'll have them for breakfast in a ljttle</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">while?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But neither Bat nor Nick seemed to care to accept</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">this hospitable invitation.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They acted as if they had something on their minds;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">something disagreeable, or unpleasant, which was trou-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bling them.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack noticed this, and wondered what it was.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He bad no great respect for either of the boys, nor</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cfesire for their company; but he always tried to treat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">everyone civilly, just as he would like to be treated</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">himself.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">That was one reason why Jack Lightfoot had sue!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a host of friends.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Though he was so far above these two boys in mani</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ways, he had"no feeling of superiority.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Apparently they had come out to Simm's Hole fo-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a good time, as he and his friends had, and he wa:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">willing that -they should enjoy themselves to the ut</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">most.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Finding that neither Nick nor Bat were in a talka</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tive mood, Jack gave over his efforts in that line anc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">returned to the camp.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"What are those fellows^ping here?".Lafe asked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I couldn't find out; fishing,' I presume."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I wish they'd stayed away; they'll tnake trouble.'</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Skul Messenger thrust forward his shock of yellov</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hair and his pugilistic jaw.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Let 'em try it!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot was forced to laugh.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Saul, I don't know whether you,like to fight as wel</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">as Lafevdoes to eat, though I rather think you do</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">But there is nothing to fight- about yet."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Just let 'em try to make trouble for us," said Sau!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">clinching his fists. "I've been longing for a chance t&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hammer in the face of that low-down nigger* Nic</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Flint!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That Indian, you mean!" said Lafe.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Indian or nigger, it don't make much difference t</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">me; when I get through with him he Won't know tha</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">• T</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he's got a face."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul's attitude was so much that of the eager pugilis</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that Jack laughed again; and, sitting down, with penc</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and paper, he drew a Garicature of Saul Messenger i</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the ^rct of reducing Nick Flint to something tha</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">looked* like a bag of jelly.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"That's what I'd like to do to him," said Sau</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">trying to grin, when he saw the picture. "And it</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">what I will do, if he goes to making trouble roun</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">here."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">«3</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">l^ick Flint and Bat Arnold disappeared while the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">L were eating breakfast.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[t was a fine breakfast, too, showing that Lafe</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">^ton was well up in the culinary art.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^ Td like to know where you learned to fry fish so</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">j?" *ai'd Ned Skeen. "Howling mackerels, this</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ti</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">•Not a howling mackerel, non any other kind ; that's</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">t tout. Don't disgrace it by calling it a mackerel."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">.Jed Skeen's mouth was filled with fish, but he con-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ltd to ask again how Lafe had learned the trick of</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ng them to such a turn.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">TYom my mother," said Lafe. "She's a good</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">t"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You take after, her naturally," Jack remarked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Til take after yoji," said Lafe, vWtfc a lauglr, "if</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">nlbn't jraise that fish as you ought to. It's this</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">r: I always liked to eat, you knowl"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Oh, yes, we know that I"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ISdI used to hang round the kitchen a good deal."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">h'ou used to ? Oh, that's good!''</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">I'WeJl, I do still, of course; and so, watching her,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">» helping her now and then' when she'd let me, I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">$ the hang of cooking a good many things. And I</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">5b'er like to cook."</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">j'Because you can eat whi|e you're cooking?"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fcure!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rffl: addition to the fish, there was bread, which Jerry</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"brought from the town, crackers, canned goods of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">WBs kinds, principally canned fruits, together with</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pr, eggs, condensed milk, canned vegetables and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nr things; though all of these were not served for</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nkfast. of course.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Fhe boys were living well; and they were, besides,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the time of their live3.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^ick Flint and Bat Arnold, who had refused to par-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">:e of that bountiful breakfast, were practically for-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">iten, while the boys ate, laughed and joked, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">®ned for the fishing trips of the day.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">I th going to try for that hermit trout!" said</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack. "If a fallow could hook him------"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He'd pull you into the hole," said Nat Kimball.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'd risk it. If I could once get my hook in his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">mouth, there'd be a pretty fight, anyhow, if I didn't</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">land him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Though Jackineant to try for the hermit trout which</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Peleg said inhabited Simm's Hole, he desired first to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">whip a certain section of one of the creeks of the neigh-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">borhood, where, the year before, he had had good hide.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He set out for this pojnt after breakfast, going</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">alone, as most of the other boys had plans of their own</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">for the morning, which would scatter them to various</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">places.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As Jack walked along he chanced to see Bat Arnold</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">moving in the -woods before him. It was just a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">glimpse he caught, but it set him to thirrking.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I wonder what those fellows are doing up here?</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Maybe they're making for the same point I am, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">intend to fish there."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jle hurried on.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Reaching the creek, and seeing no one, he began to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">whip the stream, carefully selecting his flies, and using</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">all the skill of which he was master.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had landed one speckled beauty, and was so</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">deeply immersed in the sport that he had again forgot-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ten about Bat and Nick and the warning which had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">teen so strangely thrown into his room.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then a club, whirled from a low tree over his head,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">struck him a* blow on the shoulder, and at the'same</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">time a form dropped out of the branches.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The club had been so aimed that if Jack had not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">shifted his position just at the instant it was thrown</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it would have struck him full on the head, and the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">form that shot downward must have struck him also.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But, hitting him on the shoulder, the injury was not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">so great, though the blow was*heavy enough to deaden</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and numb the arm.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack recovered, dropped his rod, and turned just in</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="024" facs="024"/>
                <fw place="top">24</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">time to see a disguised and masked figure spring at</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">him, striking again with a clulx</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack avoided this blow by springing backward, and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in so doing put his back against a rock.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He saw now that he had two masked enemies to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">meet; and, having seen Bat in the woods, he at once</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jumped to the conclusion that they were Bat Arnold</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and Nicholas Flint.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">His left arm and shoulder, struck by the club, pained</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and numbed by the blow, were almost useless.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Neither of his assailants uttered a word, as they</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rushed upon him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I know you, Niak," said Jack, judging that Nick</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was the one who had hit him. "Put down that club!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Instead of putting it down, Nick struck with it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With a quick jump Jack hi,t the club with his foot</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and sent it Spinning into the creek, wrenching and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">stinging the hand that had held it. ,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Believing that the two of them were more than</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">enough "to do up" Jack Lightfoot, the boys rushed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The dastardly character of this unprovoked attack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fired Jack's heart and filled him with almost an un-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">governable rage.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack had a hot temper, which he had exhibited on</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">more than one occasion, but which he tried to hold</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in check.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It burned to a fury now, and made him reckless and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">implacable. And when Jack Lightfoot was thus</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">aroused he had the quickness and the fighting power</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of a tiger.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He set his back against the rock, as they rushed in.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Though his temper was boiling, his brain was clear;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">his face was pale, and his gray-blue eyes were shining</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and wide open.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Crack!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold received a stinging blow in the face that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sent him reeling.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hampered by his injured left arm, Jack could not</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">swing again with his right in time to smash his fisj</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">into the face of Nick Flint; he only struck Flint</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the arm.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The next moment he and Flint grappled, and fell t(</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the ground together.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With his jaw feeling as if it had been broken, Ea</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had stumbled backward, and fallen into the water.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Help, here!" yelled Flint, thus revealing his identic</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">by his voice.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot had him by the throat.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat staggered up, dripping with water, and rushe&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to the aid of his friend.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack tripped him with'his foot as he came on, am</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bart: fell on top of the struggling boys.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In the wild struggle that ensued, Nick Flint release</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">himself; and then, mistaking Bat for Jack Lightfooi</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he began to hammer him in the face.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat yelled for all he was worth.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Before Nick understood what he was doing, Jac</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lightfoot had writhed out of his grasp and sprun</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to his feet.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">t</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick and Bat rolled apart.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">#</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick now whipped out a knife.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Seeing that in his possession, Jack again backe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">against the rock.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The numbness and pain were going out of his ir</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jured arm. Even if that had not been ?o, Jack Ligh!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foot would have forgotten the injury now, or ignore</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Both of his assailants rushed at him again, Xic</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">with the knife, cursing furiously.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In the scuffle on the ground Nick's hat zlnd mae</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had fallen off, and his dark Apache face was now r-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">vealed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat still had his mask on, but that hammering ha</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">twisted it awry, revealing a bruised and swollen chee</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">where Nick's hammering fist had done its work.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Come on!" Jack yelled, wild and defiant. "Con</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">on, you cowards!--you sneaks 1 Come onj"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="025" facs="025"/>
                <fw place="top">25</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">[p'hey were accepting the invitation.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">[jack dodged to avoid the knife; and,1 feidting, drove</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Is strong right fist into Nick's face.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He struck at Bat with his other fist almost at the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ne time. But the blow was /lot so effective, and Bat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ided one that jarred Jack's head and made it sing.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tThe knife was knocked from Nick's'hand by his fall;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">d while he was trying to recover it, Jack threw his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">t arm about Bat Arnold's neck and plunged his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">■ong right fist into his face.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was a bad-looking countenance after that. Bat</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">wled. Jack struck again, in his rage. Bat fell,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">iply; and Jack released him, just as Nick rushed in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ain.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You murdering coward, I'll settle you!" Jack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">■earned.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He drove a terrific blow at Nick, and received a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">•ust from the knife that ripped the sleeve of his coat;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in struck again; and this time with a force so ef-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">:tive that both knife and boy went into the creek.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat was trying to get up.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack jumped at him, with his foot lifted tp deliver</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">cick.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">''Don't! don't!" Bat groaned. "You've killed me</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">w; don't!"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">N'ick Flint was thrashing the water with his hands.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">*</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tack again backed against the rock and stood ready</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">-his enemies.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">5at crept to his feet, groaning; one of his eyes</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">s closed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">S«ick flounced, and flailed at the water.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'He's drowning!" said Bat, with a hoarse cry.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">an't you see?"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ack was still furious.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'Help him out, then!" he shouted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">'But I--I can't; you put him there!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">rt was true.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">tack looked at Arnold. His brain was clearing; that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">terrific fit of passion which had made him so tigerish</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and so furious in the fight was passing.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He saw that Nick Flint seemed to be growing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">weaker and was in no condition to aid himself.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"You won't jump at me?" he asked of Bat.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat, with his. hands to hi6 face, groaned as a reply.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack passed him with a quick leap; and, springing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">into the stream, caught Nick Flint by the arm and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">literally pulled him out of the creek.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick was gasping and strangling, and seemed but</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">half conscious.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A feeling of remorse, mingled with something al-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">most like fear, swept over Jack. The thought that he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">might have killed Nick came tp startle him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Seeing that Bat was not likely to renew the attack</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">he bent over Flint now and began some effort to re-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">store him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick was a hardy youngster, who was not likely to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">give up easily; and he soon came out of his confused</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">state, which would have brought his death no doubt</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">if he had remained in the water.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He looked almost shamefaced, when he saw that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it was Jack Lightfoot who was. aiding him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat, with his mask awry, his clothing rumpled and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">torn, s^ood by the rock, one eye swollen shut, and his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">features badly battered.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat had had enough and to spare.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Just then there was a crashing in the underbrush.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul Messenger, the fighting man of the fishing</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">crowd, came upon the scene.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had seen something of that furious struggle</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">from a distance, and to his great regret had been too</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">far away to take part in it.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Just let me at 'em!" he panted.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"No," said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Don't--don't let him hit me!" Bat begged, pite</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ousfy.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Stand back!" Jack commanded, speaking sharply</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to Saul.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="026" facs="026"/>
                <fw place="top">26</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was a picture for an artist, Jack Lightfoot, strong,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">slender, his handsome face pale^ but unmarred, his</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">gray-blue eyes flashing, as he waved back; Saul Mes-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">senger with that commanding gesture.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul himself, rushing forward, with fists clinched,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">hat off, his yellow hair tousled over his head like a</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">shock of wheat, his sturdy, pugilistic jaw thrust out.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bat Arnold--bullet-headed Bat--limping away, to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">escape Saul's rush, his coat tOm, his disarranged mask</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">hanging over one ear, one eye closed, and his face</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">bruised and bloody.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">And on the ground, his clothing soaked, his hat</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">gone, his Indian-like visage scratched and pummelcd,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Nick Flint, of the1 murderous heart and the Apache</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">temper.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then there was th» trout Stream, fringed by trees;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the open path through the woods; and*the murmuring,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">purling brook; with a fish line and fod on the ground,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">and a small trout beside them.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Stand back I" &gt; Jack comrhanded, with imperious</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">gesture.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Fighting Saul fell back before that stern order and</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the fire of those eyes.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"They're in no'condition to fight," said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"And you'll let them go scot-free?" Saul protested.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Yes; they may go how, for all I care; and the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">sooner they get out the better I shall be pleased."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER IX.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">TAKING THE HERMIT TROUT.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot stood on the rim of the broken dam,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">by the cabin, flinging his trout fly out into Simm's</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Hole.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had been doing that for more than an hour, try-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing different -flies.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"The felly's wantin' a gold bug," said Jerry.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Common throut- flies, made out av feathers ah' the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^Joike, ain't good enough for 'um."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Silently Jack tried another fly, and cast again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The boy^ of the camp were in various places, e</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gaged in various things.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">In the cabin door almost behind Jack stood La</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lampton and Bob Brewster.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">With them was Orson 0*x, who had appeared</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the camp during'the day, wearing something of tnj</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fefy. and nervousness in his manner.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The stqry Orson had heard of the attack on Jac</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and the manner in which Jack had *Haid out" his s</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sailants, had caused Orson, to assurhe a still more si</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gular aiT.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">It was known that Orson followed often In the tr:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of Nick Flint, and the boys accounted Jor his que</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">manner in that way; yet Orson had not said a word-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">defense of Nick and Bat.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As for those thoroughly whipped youngsters, th</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">had headed for town as soon as they were in a co</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">dition to travel.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"I'll try the old hermit with a silver fly, this time</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said Jack, smiling, as he prepared to try yet aga</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Here's a silver one with black spots, making it lo&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">like a spotted butterfly;"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Ut will have to be a gold wan or- a diamond war</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jerry insisted. "So cheap a thing as silver cai</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">timpt a delicate crayter loike* that. He's so shy</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">must be Irish; tHry him wid a grane wan."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"We're making too much noise," said Jack.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">•He stepped back, to get his shadow off the wat&lt;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and tried other flies.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">A plump butterfly, one of the earliest of the seaSC</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">came batting by, and flopping into the hole.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Instantly there was a swirl of the water, a monsl</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">trout.rose, and the butterfly was gone.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"By the cove av Cork, did yees see that? tJt w</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Him! He was big as an ellyphant," said Jerry, in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hoarse whisper.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Peleg said as big as a whale."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">''He wuz that, begorra! Oh, the iligant cravthe</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="027" facs="027"/>
                <fw place="top">27</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">he's wantin' real mate; no bugs made out av</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">kgs and the loikes fer him."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fberc's another one of those butterflies," cried#Ned</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">FJpid he took after the mate of the first, with</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">t.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">fe returned with it in a little while, having knocked</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">kwn and killed it.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bck set it on his hook; and with a flirt sent it out</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jihe hole</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Tie butterfly settled on the water, and with wings</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^jd floated along while Jack, moving his pole</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">^tly, tried to give it a simulation of fife? as if it</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">'Struggling to rise from the water.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">He plants his mate alive I" whispered Jerry. "Oh,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pe'ticklar crayther! He don't want anny butther</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">that's been knocked on the head an' kilt, bedad !H</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">[did seem so.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">a:k moved his rod, and the butterfly, apparently</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">g, seemed on the point of lifting itself from</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pool.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hen there was a swirl of the water, as a shadow</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">led to dart from under the dam; this was followed</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">flashing leap--then the line straightened,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">lere was a sudden splash, a flash of silver in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ttid a shout from Lafe; for Jack Lightfoot had</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lily hooked the foxy old trout of the-* swimming</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ie reel sang!</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rry threw his hat into the air and yelled,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fegorra. ye've got him! Can yees howld him?"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ie hooked trout went to the bottom of the hoLe;</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Seemed determined to make wildly for the lake-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">-h paid the line out, and when it eased, he began</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">il In.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">am the trout struck out for a healthier climate,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">•nee more the speeding line made the reel hum.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">00k out er he'll br-reak yer line; he'll shnap yer</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ftke a broom sthraw !"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">&amp; was well aware of that.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He knew that skill alone could land that big trout.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Feeling t,he wrench of'the hook it threw itself out</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">of the water, in a dear leap that showed its big body</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and superb markings.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">%</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howly slimoke, did yees see 'um!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The trout, having made that leap, was coming up-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">stream.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The reel spun under Jack's fingers as he took in the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">line.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Under the edge of the dam the trout darted; then</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">stopped and lay there.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"He's home, an' he knows it; an' he won't come out."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack brought him out by a lift, of the rod ; and again-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the startled trout headed downstream.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack was playing the big" fish with' consummate</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">skill, having a care all, the time for the security of his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">line and rod.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When he could he tightened the line, in an effort to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tire and discourage the^rout; when he could do noth</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ing else he let the reel sing, yet with enough pressure</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to give the line a continuous pull.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Again the great fish threw himself out of the water,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in a skipping jump; and again Jerry and the other</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">boys roared.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">v Peleg Brown came up on the shore and fairly</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">danced, clapping his hands, when he saw the fight that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was on.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">For years he had tried to lure that trou^ to his hook,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">*</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">and once he had succeeded, only to let him get away</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">again.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howled 'um !" Jerry cfied.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack was "holding him!" He was doing more, he</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">was tiring the big fish.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Up and down, from end to end and side to side of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the hole, the trout rushed, feeling the pull of the hook</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">constantly. He threw himself from the water in great</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">leaps, and sinking to the bottom sulked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then, when forced to start again, he repeated the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">same tactics, over and over.</span>
                    </ab>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="028" facs="028"/>
                <fw place="top">28</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The fight was on. The slender rod and compara-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">tively weak line, and the skill of a boy, were matched</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">against the strength of the big fish.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">But the skill of the boy was'telling.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">For more than half an hour the combat lasted; then,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">when Jack thought the trout was wora out, the strug-.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">gle started anew, and continued for another fifteen</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">minutes, until Jack began to find that he was getting</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pretty tired himself, in spite of the thrill and the ex-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">/</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">citement.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe grabbed the landing net, as Jack, walking</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">along the dam. toward the shore, began to lead the ex-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hausted fish in that direction.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Where there's one trout there's always its mate,"</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">said Ned Skeen, and he threshed his line into the ptiol</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">where the fish had been hooked.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Lafe thrust his landing pet under the big trout,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">which Jack drew to the shore*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Within the cabin, looking from the door, Bob Brew-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ster and Orson Oxx, who had been hopping Up'.and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">down in their excitement, joined hands, and began to</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">sing and dance with joy, roaring out the words of a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fishing song.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">As they thus danced and roared, they broke the half</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">rotten boards of the floor, and Bob Brewster dropped'</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">through with a yell.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">At the same instant there wa§ a terrific splash under</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the edge of ♦the dam.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then there was another yell, Jliis time in the voice of</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Howling mackerels," Kfe exclaimed, "I've got a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">bigger one!1''</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">His rod bent almost double as he tugged and</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">strained.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He began to pull in*-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Here fellows," he called, "help me; he'll get away</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">from me!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack Lightfoot and Jerry Mulligan were busy in</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">getting the big trout out of the water.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Saul Messenger rushed to Skeen's assistance.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Play hjim easy," he said, putting out his hand</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">take? hold of'the rod; "play him easy, or he'll bre</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">your pole.'*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Then both he and Ned Skeen stared, as well</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">howled, for the thing that came to the surface was n</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a fish--but a man!</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">C</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER X.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE RESCUE.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Throwing the big trout well up on the shore, whei</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">it could not possibly get back into the hole, Jack LighJ</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">foot, Lafe Lampton and Jerry Mulligan raced oi</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">upon the broken dam to the assistance of Ned Skeei</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The boys in the cabin came out also; followed b</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">Bob, who had dragged himself from the hole int</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">which he had tumbled, and who was not hurt by hi</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fall.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Ned Skeen's hook had caught in the man's coat, i)]</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">the back, between the shoulders, and being a strong</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hook, with a good line, it was holding.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The man was threshing the water wildly with hi:</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hands, and seemed unable to swim.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When Jack observed this, he threw aside his coatj</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">kicked off his shoes* and sprang into the hole.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jerry Mulligan imitated him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">They came up by the man, as he was rising once</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">more to the surface.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Skeen's hook Was still in the man's, coat, and Skeef,,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">in spite of his nervous and excited condition, was st-^</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hanging to the rod.'</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">"Now, get him by that side, Jerry!" said Jack. "And</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">be careful that he don't get you*"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The warning was needed; for the man, in his fright</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">ened and wholly irresponsible condition, was trying</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">to lay hold of something.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He caught Jerry by tbe coaf and ducked him uftder.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Jack evaded the clutch of his hand, and then secured</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a grip of his coat. f</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL-SPORTS LIBRARY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab/>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="029" facs="029"/>
                <fw place="top">29</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Iime up, with the man still clinging to him.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">m wan!" he begged. "He's dhrownin' me."'</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">shed water in the man's face; and sought to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">p.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">-rent was doing the rest; for it was setting</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">award the shore below,* on the same side,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ampton, having thrown off coat and shoes,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">now, and came swimming boldly to the as-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">F Jack and Jerry.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">time the man whom the boys were Trying to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">s so nearly drowned that he was helpless to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">If of injure those who were trying to aid</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">een had* cut his line; and all the boys were</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ng round to the shore on that side, to render</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">they could.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">he current threw the swimmers in-dose to</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">they drew the man to the land; and then all</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">d lifted at him until he was out,of the water</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ip on the dry ground.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">n then the victory was not won, for brisk</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">e required to bring hint back to life,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">hey made these efforts they made also a</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">prising discovery.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">The man was clothed in two complete suits; the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">jtter one being a thing of shreds and patches, the</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">IWer.one of respectable cut, make and cloth.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">The man was well along in years, and bearded; his</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">fetd being somewhat shaggy, and his hair and eye-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">pvvs grayish.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">iWilson Crane, who had joined thd fishing party that</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">prning, stared, thrusting his long, nose forward is if</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">|fished to probe the man in the face with.it.</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">('Say, fellows," he exclaimed, in a hoarse whisper,</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">&gt;is is the Wild Man!"</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">CHAPTER XL</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE MYSTERIES CLEARED AWAY.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Wilson Crane at various times had talked a great</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">deal about the Wild Man, who had been seen by differ-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ent persons in the vicinity of Cranford.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Wilson had seen this so-called Wild Man once him-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">self; and at another time, thinking he was to get a sec*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ond look at him, he had stumbled upon some tramps</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">who were holding Jack Lightfoot a prisoner in The</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Painted Cave.*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When seen by Wilson and other people of Cranford,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">the Wild Mart had been clothed in these tattered outer</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">clothes, and no one guessed that he had a good suit</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">underneath them.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The efforts of Jack Lightfoot and his friends to re-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">store the so-called Wild Man to consciousness were</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">effective, after a time; and the fellow, sitting up,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">stared about hinfvjn a strange way.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Befofe this occurred Bob Brewster had told a queer</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">story of finding a small room below the cabin floor.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">He had tumbled into that room, falling upon an old</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">coat, which was rolled up as if it'had been used as a</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">bed.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The search which some of the boys now made</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">\</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">brought other things to light, among them a queei*</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">stovepipe arrangement, covered with dirty white cloth,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">which the Wild Man had used, setting it upon his</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">shoulders to give him a supernatural height.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">When the Wild Man looked around in that strange</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">way, observed the excited group of boys gathered</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">about him, and saw his wet clothing, he doubled him-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">self together, and, shaking his thin sides, laughed like'</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">a hyena. I</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">*See last week's issue, No. 4--"Jack Lightfoot's Athletic Tour-</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">nament ; or, Breaking the Record Quarter-Mile Dash.'</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This library represents an entirely new idea. It is totally different from any other now</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">published. The stories detail the adventures of three plucky lads who set out to capture the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">notorious Captain Kidd. Every real boy has longed to read more about the doings of this bold</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">marauder of the seas and the opportunity is now given them.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The stories are of generous length and without equals in thrilling adventure and interest.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">The best sea stories ever written.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">1. Captain Kidd's Sea Swoop ; or, Carried Off by Pirates.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">2. Captain Kidd's. Buried Treasure; or, Adventures of Three Boys Among the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Buccaneers.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">3. The Silver Cutlass ; or, Thad and His Chums Dost in the Swamp.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">4. Defying the Sea Wolf; or, Thad at Bay in the Powder Magazine.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">5. The Jolly "Red Raven" ; or, Captain Kidd's Daring Raid on Old'New York.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">6. The Corsair Captain ; or, Thad and His Chums Afloat.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">7. The Death's Head Rovers ; or, How Thad Outwitted the Coast Freebooters.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">8. Walking the Plank ; or, The Last Cruise of the Flying-Scud.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">9. Captain Kidd's Revenge ; or, Thad Among the Tigers of the Sea.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">10. The Chest of Doubloons ; or, How Three Boys Defied the Buccaneers.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">11. The Rival Pirates ; or, Thad and His Chums in Irons.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">12. Captain Kidd's Stratagem ; or, Simple Simon Takes Soundings.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">13. The Red Raven's Prize; or, How Young Thad Sailed a Pirate Barque.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">14. Nailed to the Mast; or, The Last of Captain Kidd's "Hole in the Wall."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">15. Captain Kidd's Long Chase ; or, Thad and. His Chums in the Tropics.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">16. Set Adrift By Pirates ; or, Thad's Adventures in the Saragossa Sea.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">17- To Sink or Swim ; or* Thad and His Friends On Blue Water.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">18. Captain Kidd's Drag-Net; or, How Young Thad Hoodwinked the Buccaneers.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">19. The Phantom Pirate ; or, Thad and His Chums on the Haunted Ship.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">So. The Winged Witch ; or, How Three Boys Saved the Treasure Galleon.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">21. Captain Kidd in New Orleans; or, The Pirate Scourge of the Rigolets.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">22. Tiger of the Sea ;, or, The Three Castaways of the Gulf.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">23. The Pirates of The&gt; Keys ; or, Our Boys Afloat on the Spanish Main.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">24. Captain Kidd at Bay ; or, Marooned On a Sand-Spit.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">FIVE</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">For sale by cell newsdealers, or sent postpaid</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">upon receipt of price by the publishers</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE WINNER LIBRARY CO., 2 Duane St., New Yorii</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE RED RAVEN LIBRARY</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">THRILLING SEA STORIES</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">LATEST TITLES |</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">1. JACK LIGHTFOOT'S CHALLENGE;' "</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or, The Winning of the Wager</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">2. JACK LIGHTFOOT'S HOCKEY TEAM;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or, The Rival Athletes of Old Cranford</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">3. JACK LIGHTFOOT'S GREAT PLAY.;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or, Surprising the Academy Boys</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">4. JACK LIGHTFOOT'S ATHLETIC TOURNA-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">MENT; or, Breaking the Record Quarter-Mile Dash</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">5. JACK LIGHTFOOT IN THE WOODS;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or, Taking the Hermit Trout of Simms' Hole</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">6. JACK LIGHTFOOT'S TRUMP CURVE;</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or, The Wizard Pitcher of the Four-Town League</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">This library may be purchased from any newsdealer at five cents per copy,</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">or any number will be sent postpaid upon receipt of six cepts by</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">THE WINNER LIBRARY COMPANY, 2 Duane St., NEW YORK</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab/>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div type="page">
                <pb n="01" facs="01"/>
                <fw place="top">1</fw>
                <div type="column">
                    <cb n="01"/>
                    <ab> </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">Come, Boys, Come. Get fhe</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">ALL=SPORTS</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">LIBRARY</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">" Teach the American boy how to become, an athlete and Idjy the</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">foundation of a constitution greater than that of the United Slates."</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">-- Wise sayings from Tip Top.</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">You like fun, adventure, and mystery don't you? Wefl, youtu 3ind them</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">all in the pages of the stories in this library. As the name implies, tike ALL-</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">SPORTS LIBRARY-.is devoted to the sports all young people delight in. It</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">has bright handsome cblpred covers, and each story is at least 30,000 words in</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">length. You are looking for a big five cents worth of good reading'and you can</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">get it here. Ask your newsdealer for any t&gt;f the titles listed belofo. He has</span>
                    </ab>
                    <ab>
                        <span type="columnLine">them in stock. v</span>
                        <span type="columnLine">PRICE, FIVE CENTS</span></ab>
                </div>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>